Q22: What is different about the output from last time? Which branches are you on?
Initially running git branch results in ‘* main’. After checking out from the main branch
 and creating a new branch called feature1, we are presented with a list of created
 branches with the branch that we are currently on, highlighted in green.


Q30: Run ls. Is there anything different?
What’s weird about the results running ls after switching from branch feature1 back to
 main, is that the new text file ‘inspiration.txt’ isn’t listed under the main branch.

Q33: running gitk opens a new window that shows the history of commits with information about the authors, modification times, and commit history.